Full Stack Software Development

ZHOUWU HUANG

→ huangzhouwu@gmail.com

15900517866

EXPERIENCE

HASCO Vision Technology (Shanghai) Co., Ltd. Head of Digital Development Department | November 2021 - Now

I was responsible for the key online teaching system development (including scheduling course, user problem ticket management, teacher payment modules) and Automation Platform(to support online Time sheet, contract approval, IT help desk and automation test process). Communicated with BA team to understand the business requirements, took ownership of outstanding deliverable (design solutions, code construction, test and technical documents). Researched advanced technology regarding best practice and drove best practice within the team.

Shanghai ALO7 Technology Co., Ltd.

Software Development Expert | December 2017 - August 2021

I was responsible for the key online teaching system development (including scheduling course, user problem ticket management, teacher payment modules) and Automation Platform(to support online Time sheet, contract approval, IT help desk and automation test process). Communicated with BA team to understand the business requirements, took ownership of outstanding deliverable (design solutions, code construction, test and technical documents). Researched advanced technology regarding best practice and drove best practice within the team.

Omni Prime Inc.

Automation Testing Architect | October 2016 - December 2017

Worked on the Internet Finance online system(peer-to-peer lending), I was responsible for building and developing automation test strategy, framework, and tool platform. Basic services such as gateway, service registration discovery, load balancing, permissions, security, control center, dictionary, SMS platform and other modules. I have a deep understanding in micro service interface test, integration test, contract test, component test, Docker Web UI test, App cloud test and so on.

Pactera Technology Co. Ltd.

Senior Delivery Manager | May 2008 - October 2016

Worked on the Home and Small Business Server testing project, I was responsible for making test strategy, test plan and providing test deliveries (test cases design, test cases execution, test report, bugs submission). Test management including resource management, risk management, schedule management, stakeholder management, training and so on.

Augmentum, Inc.

Software Development Engineer in Test | July 2007 - May 2008

Worked on Microsoft ERP product Dynamics AX testing project, I was responsible for requirement analysis, test case high level design, test case low level design, test case review, automation scripts coding, defects submission and status track, test reports, knowledge sharing and test documents.

EDUCATION

South China University of Technolog (Project 985 elite university)

Bachelor of Science (Mathematics) | September 2003 - June 2007

SKILLS

About me

Hello! I have sixteen years of experience in software development. I have extensive experience in ERP system solutions, desktop operating system solutions, internet financial industry, internet education industry, traditional automobile manufacturing information digitalization. I am an enthusiastic software engineer passionate about technology, and I enjoy delving into and using new technologies and applying them to appropriate scenarios. I hope to have the honor of working with you!